managerleague.com 2015-12-06

# Online Football Manager

We take great pride in welcoming you to ManagerLeague! A game filled with fun, football, frustration, enjoyment, surprises, hate, love, shock, wins, losses, untrustworthy systems, rubbish referees, terrible gains, good gains, fantastic transfer-deals, not-so-fantastic transfer-deals, friendlies, league-cups, department-cups, Champions League, The Super-Cup, great youngsters, not-so-great youngsters, forum-fun, forum-spam, friendly messages, outright spam, terrible injuries, lawyers wasting money (surprise!), good match-sims and bad match-sims. There is certainly a lot to be experienced in ManagerLeague, and we are very proud of it! ManagerLeague isn't like "any other football-manager game", it's different, and some times VERY different. It's fast, action-packed and certainly demanding, sometimes outright annoying. And we wouldn't want it any other way! Nor would you! If you haven't joined yet, do so now, and if you have joined us already, go on in! Good luck!!! 

May 1st, 2010

At Fifth Season we recognize that privacy is important. This Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Fifth Season AS (collectively,Fifth Season's "services"). In addition, where more detailed information is needed to explain our privacy practices, we post separate privacy notices to describe how particular services process personal information.

If you have any questions about this Policy, please feel free to contact us through [email](mailto:webmaster@managerleague.com) or through our website.

**Information we collect and how we use it:**

  * **Information you provide** \- When you sign up for a ManagerLeague account or other Fifth Season service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password). We may combine the information you submit under your account with information from other Fifth Season services or third parties in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services. For certain services, we may give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information.  
We never share or give out your registered information that is regarded as private. Private information like name and addresses are only used for purposes of identification or when sending out prizes won in competitions and similar activities. Your email address is used for identification, sending your password or to send you other important game-related information. We also send out a newsletter now and then, but no more than 6 times per year. You can easily opt out of this newsletter in your preferences. Finally, we may use your regional information to provide you with regional content or advertising, like results from regional matches or regional news.
  * **ManagerLeague cookies** \- When you visit ManagerLeague, we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service by storing user preferences. Cookies are required to use our services, but they hold no personal information. 
  * **Log information** \- When you use Fifth Season services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit a website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser. 
  * **User communications** \- When you send email or other communication to Fifth Season, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services. 

Fifth Season only processes personal information for the purposes described in the applicable Privacy Policy and/or privacy notice for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our products and services to users, including the display of customized content and advertising; 
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services; 
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our network; and 
  * Developing new services. 

You can find more information about how we process personal information by referring to the privacy notices for particular services. 

Fifth Season processes personal information on our servers in Norway. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.

**Choices for personal information**

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Policy and/or in the specific service notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Fifth Season may not be able to provide those services to you. 

**Information sharing**

Fifth Season only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Fifth Season in the following limited circumstances: 

  * We have your consent. We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information. 
  * We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. 
  * We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against imminent harm to the rights, property or safety of Fifth Season, its users, its services, or the public as required or permitted by law. 
  * We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users clicked on a particular advertisement. Such information does not identify you individually. 

**Information security**

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data. 

We restrict access to personal information to Fifth Season employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations. 

**Data integrity**

Fifth Season processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

**Accessing and updating personal information**

When you use Fifth Season services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users' personal information. We provide the details for these procedures in the specific privacy notices or FAQs for these services. 

**Enforcement**

Fifth Season regularly reviews its compliance with this Policy. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between Fifth Season and an individual. 

**Changes to this policy**

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Policy changes). Each version of this Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date.
